A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - Tusteeships, Universities and Institutes, 1954-1976
    - Franklin Institute, 1966-1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Franklin Institute, Bartol Research Foundation, 1967-1975 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Franklin Institute, Biochemical Research Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Franklin Institute, Biochemical Research Foundation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Franklin Institute, Center for Naval Analysis, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - General Education Board, 1954-1964 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Haifa University, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Harvard Industries Inc., 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1958-1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1970-1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Institutional Scientific Research, International House Jubilee Campaign, 1953-1974
    - Southwest Center for Advanced Studies, 1962-1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Tulane University, Board of Visitors, 1961-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Tulane University, Delta Regional Primate Center, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1960-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Wave Hill Center for Environmental Studies, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Webster College, 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Leonard Wood Memorial, American Leprosy Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, 1953-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, Dean Selection Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, Education Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, Organization, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - World's Fair Corporation, 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - World's Fair Corporation, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - World's Fair Corporation, 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - International House Jubilee Campaign, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - International House Jubilee Campaign, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - International House Jubilee Campaign, Ambassador Davis, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - International House Jubilee Campaign, Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Organizational Committee Work, Johnson/Humphrey Campaign, 1957-1973
    - U.S. Department Health, Education and Welfare, National Advisory Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - U.S. China Relations, Inc., National committee, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - U.S. President's Special Committee on Civilian Honors, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Senate, Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1956-1960 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Department of Navy, Bureau of Medicine and Surgery, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Intergovernmental Relations Hearing, 1967 March 8 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Department of State, Agency for International Development, 1962 August 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - World Leprosy Day, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - United Nations Association, Panel on China, UN and U.S. Policy, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - U.S. - Japan Committee on Scientific Cooperation, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - U.S. - Japan Committee on Scientific Cooperation, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Dept of Defense, Defense Science Board, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, World Food Congress, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Selective Service System, 1955-1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - United Nations Conference on Science and Technology, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Scientific Research in a Modern State, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Science Fair Committee, American Institute, NYC, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - President's Committee on the National Medal of Science, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Committee for the Princeton Council for International Studies, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Population Crisis Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Planned Parenthood World Population, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Trinity School, Councils of Sponsors 250th Anniversary, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Spence-Chapin Awards Committee, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Sigma Xi, Executive Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Scientists and Engineers for Johnson/Humphrey, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Scientists and Engineers for Johnson/Humphrey, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Department of HEW, Bureau of Disease Prevention and Environmental Control, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - National Committee on International Cooperation Year, White House Conference, 1965 November 28-December 1 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - National Committee on International Cooperation Year, White House Conference, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - National Council for Civic Responsibility of the Public Affairs Institute, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - U.S. President's Committee on Scientists, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - U.S. Congress Select Committee of Government Research, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Williams College, Mt. Hope Farm, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Committee of the West Side Association of Commerce, Testimonial Dinner Nov 18, 1965, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Weizmann Institute of Science, International Committee for the 25th Anniversary, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - U.S. President's Committee on Scientists and Engineers, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Government Operations, 1958-1965 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Westinghouse Electric Time Capsule Committee, NY World's Fair, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Westinghouse Electric Time Capsule Committee. NY World's Fair, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Organizational Committee Work, 1958-1975
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), National Research Council (NRC), 1964-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - NAS, NRC, 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - NAS, Joint Board of NAS, National Academy of Engineering, 1961-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - NAS Finance Committee, 1963-1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - NAS, NRC, 1952-1962 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Educational Broadcast Company, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Committee: Miscellaneous File, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Health Research Council - NY City, 1858-1965 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Science Advisor to the Mayor of New York, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - NY City Science and Technology Advisory Council to Mayor John V. Lindsay, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Fort Totten, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - NY City - City University of New York, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - NY City - Welfare Island Development Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corp., Cooperative Council (Channel 13, WNDT), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Emmy Awards, New York Area, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Journal of Inter-American Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary - 80th Anniversary, (Committee of Sponsors), 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Israel Education Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Third International Congress of Food Science and Technology, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Interagency Committee on Oceanography, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - New School for Social Research, 50th Anniv. Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - NY City American Public Health Association, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, Scientific and Technical Personnel, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Navy Research Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - East-West Center, 1962-1967 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Family of Man (Awards Ceremony), 1968 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Thomas A. Edison Birthday Celebration Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Biomedical Engineering Committee, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Coordinating Council on Education for the Disadvantaged, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Columbia University, International Section of Program of Continuing Education, School of Public Health, etc., 1961-1965 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Citizens Organized Against Drug Abuse Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Citizens for Transportation Progress Committee, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Citizens for Javits Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Citizens for a Quieter City (NYC) Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Corning Science Prize Book, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Dickinson College, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - New York State Science Advisory Council, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - New York State Science Advisory Council, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - New York Statewide Advisory Committee on Engineering, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - New York State Advisory Council for the Advancement of Research and Development, 1959-1970 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement, 1964-1974 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Fluoridation Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Fund for Overseas Research Grants and Education, 1962-1975 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Monument Committee, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - NRC, Committee to Study Advisory Services to Government, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - NRC, Committee to Study Advisory Services to Government, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Science Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - U.S. Bicentennial Celebrations, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - U.S. Bicentennial Celebrations, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Organizational Committee Work, 1956-1974
    - Bronx County Golden Jubilee (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Atlantic Council of the United States, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American Society of European Chemists, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Museum of Natural History, Centennial Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American Library in Paris, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American Council on Education, Ad hoc Committee on Education in Predominantly Negro Colleges, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American Foreign Service Association, Committee of Judges for Awards, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Academy of Natural Sciences, Department of Limnology, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Albany Institute of History and Art, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Brookings Institution, Committee on Problems of the American Community, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Balzan Prize, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Committee of Arts and Sciences for Eisenhower, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Catalyst, 1962-1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - California Museum of Science and Industry, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Center for NYC Affairs, New School for Social Research, 1964-1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Century 21, National Planning Board, 1958-1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Dreyfus Foundation, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Albert Einstein Award Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - East-West Center, 1961-1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Educational Interchange Policy, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Council of State Governments, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, 1965-1973 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Harvard-MIT Program in Health Sciences, National Sponsoring Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - NASA Panel on Desynchronosis, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Marshall Scholarships, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - University of Texas, Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - The Graduate Journal, University of Texas, Editorial Advisory Board, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Michelson-Morley Award Committee, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - National Advisory Board for R/V Alpha Helix, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - International Brain Research Organization, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Institute for the Study of Man, 1957-1967 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Industrial Research, Advisory Board, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - The Impact of Science and Technology on Peace and War, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - L'Institut de la Vie, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Immigration Reform, National Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Heart Foundation, Princess Liliane of Belgium, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Health Information Foundation Citizens Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Health For Peace, 1958-1960 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - National Citizens Committee to Save Education and Library Funds, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - National Citizens Committee to Save Education and Library Funds, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - National Research Committee (NRC) Vision Committee, 1941-1946
    - Color Blindness, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Dark Adaption, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Dark Adaption, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Goggles, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Goggles, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Applied Psychology Panel, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Army/Navy/National Research Council Vision Committee, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - NRC Subcommittee on Clothing, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - National Research Council, Subcommittee on Decompression Sickness, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - National Defense Research Council (NDRC), 1941-1945 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - NDRC, 1941-1944 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - NDRC, re Phosphorescence, 1942-1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New London Submarine Base Night Vision, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - New London Submarine Base Night Vision, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Army Air Forces, 1942-1945 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Army Instrument Flying Series, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Committee of Aviation Medicine, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Navy Reports, 1943-1943 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Medals and Awards (Box 24)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Mission to Latin America, 1969
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Latin American Trip to Dominican Republic, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Ecuador, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, El Salvador, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Guatamala, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Haiti, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Honduras, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Jamaica, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Mexico, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Mexico, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Mexico, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Nicaragua, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Panama, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Paraguay, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Paraguay, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Paraguay, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Peru, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Trinidad, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Uruguay, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Venezuela, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - NAR Latin American Trip, Working Papers A-M, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Latin American Trip, Working Papers N-Z, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development (OSRD), 1942-1949
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development (OSRD), Scientific Information Policy, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - OSRD, Supplies and Equipment, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - OSRD, Surplus Property, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development (OSRD), Travel, 1942-1946 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - OSRD, Contract Proposals, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - OSRD, Baldes Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - OSRD, Barach Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bard Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bazett Contract, 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Blankenhorn Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Boothby Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Britton Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Drury Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Evans, Robley Contract, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Fender, F.A. Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Fenn Contract, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Fulton Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Fulton Contract, Vision Bibliography, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Fulton Contract, Vision Bibliography, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Hartline Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Harvey Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Hecht Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Herrington Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Hinsey Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Hitchcock Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Ivy Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Kerr Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - King Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Lamport Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Lawrence Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Low Contract, (OEMcrm-345), 1943-1945 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Lyman Contract, (OEMcmr-262) (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Millikan Contract, (OEMcmr-26), 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Orban Contract, OEMcmr-559), 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Rawson Contract, OEMcmr-28), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Ricketts Contract, OEMcmr-559, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Ryan Contract, (OEMcmr-278), 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Swarthmore Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Tyler Contract, (OEMcmr-282), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Wald Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Warden Contract, (OEMcmr-264), 1943-1945 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Wendt Contract, (OEMcmr-279 and M5665), 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Wilkins Contract, (OEMcmr-143), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Zander Contract, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Contract Renewal, (OEMcmr-28 and OEMsr-295), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - General Correspondence, (0EMsr-205), 1942-1946 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Interim Reports, (OEMsr-205), 1944 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Megohm Bridges, (0EMsr-205), 1944 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Patents, (OEMsr-205), 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - OSRD, Priorities, (OEMsr-205), 1942-1945 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Table Subscriptions, Panama, (OEMsr-205), 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Zetec, James, (OEMsr-205), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Records of Invention, (OEMcmr-209), 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Contract Renewal, (OEMcmr-209), 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - General Reports, (0EMsr-12), 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development (OSRD) Report, "Oximeters for Use in Aircraft, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Inventory on sr-12 and Material Willed to cmr26, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - OSRD, Correspondence, (OEMcmr-26), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Final Report - Lilly (OEMcmr-28), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Altitude Chamber Insurance, (OEMcmr-28), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Final Report, (OEMcmr-28), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - General Reports, (OEMcmr-28), 1941-1944 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Chamber Construction, (OEMcmr-28), 1942 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, (OEMcmr-28), 1942-1946 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Patent Applications, (OEMcmr-28), 1943-1947 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Contract Renewal (OEMsr-12), 1942-1945 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - OSRD Correspondence, (OEMsr-12), 1942-1944 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - OSRD Progress Reports, (OEMcmr-28), 1942-1945 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - OSRD General Reports, (OEMsr-26), 1945-1947 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Reproduction of Report RS/68-100, (OEMcmr-26), 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - C-K Oxygen Unit, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Candle Report, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Property Accounting (OEMcmr-26), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Property Account on sr-12, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Flight Model Oximeters, Final Report, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Final Report on Contract OEmcmr-12, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Organization, Division of Aviation Medicine, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Correspondence, (OEMcmr-209), 1941-1945 (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - General Reports, (OEMcmr-209), undated (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - General Reports, (OEMcmr-209), 1943-1949 (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Final Report, (OEMcmr-209), 1946 (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Contract Renewal, (OEMcmr-329), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - Final Report, (OEMcmr-329), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 83)
    - Correspondence, (OEMcmr-329), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 84)
    - Progress Reports, (OEMcmr-329), 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 85)
    - Contract Proposal, (OEMcmr-491), 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 86)
    - Correspondence, (OEMcmr-491), 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 87)
    - Progress Reports, (OEMcmr-491), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 88)
    - Correspondence, (OEMcmr-1975), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 89)
    - Records of Invention, (sr-1975), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - National Academy of Science (NAS), National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (NACA), 1948-1961
    - Correspondence-J, Miscellaneous, 1948-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jewett, Frank B., 1949-1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Krebiozen Project, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence-L, Miscellaneous, 1949-1952 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence-M, Miscellaneous, 1947-1953 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Marine Biological Laboratory, 1949-1959 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence-N, Miscellaneous, 1949-1953 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, National Academy of Sciences, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1949 January-March (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (NACA), 1949 April-December (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - NACA, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - NACA, 1951 January-May (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - NACA, 1951 June-December (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - NACA, 1952 January-April (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - NACA, 1952 April (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - NACA, 1952 May-December (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - NACA, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - NACA, 1954-1956 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - NACA, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - NACA, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), Air Force, 1943-1953
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), 1949 January-July (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - AEC, 1949 August-December (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - AEC, 1950 January-May (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - AEC, 1950 June-September (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - AEC, 1950 October-December (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - AEC, 1951 January-June (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - AEC, 1951 June-July (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - AEC, 1951 August-December (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - AEC, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - AEC, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - AEC, 1950-1952 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - AEC, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - AEC, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - AEC, Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - AEC, Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1950-1953 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Air Force, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Air Force, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Air Force, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Air Force, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Air Force, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 20)